[Music]  last time on sonic underground  bobby's boyfriend sagan the hedgehog  went on a summer camp vacation while  there  bobby put all his skills to the test  as well as overcoming some past trauma  of his own but now affair has been  captured by the enemy will anyone come  to his rescue or is he [ __ ]  line up boys it's time for your weekly  meal and no fighting this time or i will  punish you  ramsey stanton get off that bucket right  now trip time isn't for another four  hours oh be quiet you i will poop on my  own time by the way the bucket's full  with my rank [ __ ]  now be head tall and go fetch us a clean  bucket  ah [ __ ] please professor major cord let  me go home to my great grandson if you  can't find it in your heart to do that  then at the very least give us more food  i'm getting tired of eating my own poo  poo  you want some more food lucky for you i  am feeling generous turn around and i  will go get it for you  thank you master  you are so kind maybe after this is done  i can suck your balls as a show of my  gratitude  just who do you think is the one in  control here fool i make all the rules  here and you will take what i give you  you're so cruel and to think i was going  to suck your balls you should be the one  sucking mine  you can kill okay pinchy dungeon for me  my circle  eventually purple week i'm looking for  you i'm going to do you're okay  and we personally do the [ __ ] using  your offers oh i'm not worried about  that in fact i am quite prepared i  already have a plan motioned for all of  your little friends  all i have to do is wait for them to  trigger the trap in the meantime i'll  have some more fun with you  get over here spam ton come to daddy you  big boy  no no no please i can't take it anymore  don't let him take me at the fair can't  you do something  there is nothing i can do to save you  ramsay but there is someone else who can  a person that is ever greater than i god  keep god in your heart just like a major  chord is going to keep his balls buried  in your butt cheeks there will be no  darkness  no no no  i'm so sorry ramsay but it must be done  i do you know there  now that the professor is gone i can use  my almighty great exit the magic to  contact my friends and family for help  okay yes  but i had no other choice these are dark  times we are living robert and with  spanton's great sacrifice we just may  have a fighting chance now be on the  lookout for major chords return this is  going to take a lot of power and time  for me to accomplish  [Music]  yes but you need not worry about me  robert i must know did my powers work  are we saved now  look look with you on a  there and tell me why you see  neutering nothing stopping before  returning to the free world  no  my friend i am afraid that you must stay  here  beauty  because  if major cord finds out i am done he  will come after us  as long as you stay behind you can trick  him into thinking i am still here or  some [ __ ]  is a good thing i hid my magic robes in  this pot full of ramses sank of [ __ ]  this is goodbye for now my friend and  remember if you ever feel like giving up  just look towards god  i find that he will answer your prayers  like three percent of the time  [Applause]  do you consult there he'll be waiting  for you until you're returned  god damn it after where are you you  [ __ ]  it's almost time for the pie tasting  competition if we lose again because of  this  i'm going to stick this apple pie in my  ass and make you eat it  it's about [ __ ] time you got back  after you were gone for nine months  i was starting to think that you got  kidnapped and sold into slavery in china  or something  i have something like that  fortunately my captor was far too sexy  for that to be the case  shut up because of you we're already  late for the pie tasting competition the  other dumb [ __ ] already registered so  let's peel ass before it's too late  this sucks pie sucks i don't even like  pie  why do we gotta be here it's the weekend  i wanna go home  and play with my barbie dolls and have  can [ __ ] barbie in her stupid plastic  ass  sonia the hedgehog how on earth where  where did you learn such foul language  from you  where else  from from mindy she says it's cool to  say words that will get you grounded  i'm sorry am i in trouble am i going to  get grounded  we'll discuss that later first i want to  know where that [ __ ] you're talking  about is  she's right over there buying a funnel  cake to stick inside of her elena it's  not worth it you can't join that hill  says the association  already  plastic surgery is  i don't care mom has a job to do  stand back and hold my cigarettes  [Music]  hey there hot stuff i wanna order a  funnel cake the smallest one you got  cause him on a diet sure thing babe what  do you want on it  we got powdered sugar some jelly the  whole works do you have any lettuce  ma'am we sell funnel cakes here  well damn [ __ ] i was just asking is a  funnel cake deep fried  obviously stupid  well can you not no well then maybe i  don't want a final cake  how about that okay then leave no thanks  i think i'll keep standing right here  with my daddy for [ __ ] sake mindy stop  being a dumb woman and buy your dad a  final cake with caramel sea ripe  i didn't burn 2 000 calories this  morning to in-rip curls to listen to a  woman running her mouth  but daddy he was mean to me  well he has that right because of your  gender  you i need to have a word with you what  do you want booby face i wanna know what  the hell you've been spewing out when  you are around my daughter  i don't think that's any of your  business you [ __ ] no go before i should  stop stop italian  this isn't worth it  no charles let them be  mom stop please don't hurt her she's my  only friend  silly sonia [ __ ] can't be friends  they're too busy choking on balls for  that  welcome ladies and gentlemen to the  county fair's annual by tasting  competition  i hope you all brought your best pies  because i am happy to report that this  year i got a few extra judges with me  it is manic hedgehog and none other than  the lover of the richest and sexiest man  alive  bart levy montclair of dresden's [ __ ]  and i'm sure we all know exactly why he  offered to be a judge in this  competition  get it cause he's fat haha  hey show my bro some respect he's more  than his gay lover's personal [ __ ]  no he's not  yeah he is he's sonic the hedgehog the  blooper the fastest thing alive  wait are you saying that bartleby won't  be a judge  that's the only reason my  great-grandfather and i came here  someday if the lord above will allow it  the great bartleby montclair of dresden  will bless me in his ever-growing life  by eating a slice of my pie  but it would seem today is not that  faded day  knuckles would you take me home so that  i can cry into my pillow and ask jesus  why failed to answer my call for like  the 16th time this week  great grandfather we are not going home  yet the winner of the competition is  still walking away with 200  i ain't losing that [ __ ]  hey  why should we care about this stupid  competition if butlaby himself isn't  going to be here nobody cares about  sonic he's just a blue fat guy  i'm sorry what is your gender again  i'm a woman but i don't see why that  exactly you're a woman so either let me  touch your boobs or stop talking  because that's all women are good for  manic are you going to let him speak to  me like that i'm your girlfriend  hey don't talk to my girlfriend like  that  what are you going to do about it  grasshead  fight me  perhaps i will  no you won't now shut that pie hole  before i stuff it with the hairs in my  ass crack  quit being a wussy baby bro go over  there and stand up for your girl  i love pie i've loved pie all my life  i remember when i was just three years  old i asked my mom if i could have pie  instead of a cake for my birthday party  i know crazy right but it's true  aside from having sex with my sister it  was the best damn decision i ever made  cause when i told my mommy that i didn't  want cake  she went right down to kmart and bought  me a cherry pie instead  so i celebrated my birthday in my  backyard with all my friends and we ate  by together then my dad came home and i  was so excited to share my pie with him  but he beat my mom because she spent  money  i was scared so i wanted to call the  police but i didn't because my dad was  beating up my mom in front of the phone  so i couldn't get to it so instead i  went to hide in my closet upstairs i  took a piece of pie with me and when i  tell you that wasn't the best damn slice  of pie i ever ate in my life  i ain't joking  you may think i am but then you'd be  [ __ ] the warm gooeyness of it it  gave me a sense of warmth and comfort my  father never gave to me  nobody cares just start along with the  contest  [Music]  [Applause]  my boyfriend how could you that guy just  shot my sexy boyfriend  anyone else i thought not then let's get  this judging underway  will the first contestant please step  forward and present their pie  well daddy well mommy i'm getting bored  and i feel like winning again this year  oh baby  what can i say the choice of pie crust  is exquisite is the store bought  your assessments are correct we only use  the best from walmart and it wasn't even  marked down or on sale  impressive we're gonna have to try to  find a way to not be biased on this one  haha  this is [ __ ]  [ __ ] [ __ ] we all know bart levy  is going to win just because he rails  sonic in the ass like machine gun  don't give up just hit knuckles what if  jesus gave up we wouldn't even have this  opportunity for second place  so my lover i i mean mr montclair  can you explain to us your inspirations  for this lovely boysenberry pie  no  oh well you sort of have to if you want  to be qualified for this competition  okay perhaps i do have some baggage that  i get to tell  you see beach it all happened when i was  six years young  late in the night i had woken up from  slumber  [Music]  mommy daddy are you still awake i was  hoping you would help me make yummy  snacks for school tomorrow you see  tomorrow is going to be my sixth  birthday party and the school said i  could bring a snack to share with the  rest of the class  i wanna bring a scrumptious spy in hopes  that i can finally make a friend  shut the [ __ ] up boy can't you see mommy  and daddy are busy right now  but daddy you're not busy you're only  fighting again like you always do on the  rare chances you are both home  so what  well can't you at least tell me what it  is that you are fighting about  take a wild guess [ __ ]  your stupid mother went on another  spending spree in about half of  australia  unfortunately she forgot to kill all the  locals and now the australians from the  resistance group and are fighting back  i knew my mom and dad would have to work  overtime next week so they can kill them  so i had no choice but to go downstairs  to make their sweet pie by myself alone  [Music]  such exceptional talent young master  shall i take over while you go preheat  the oven  that's quite all right alfred i may only  be six years old but i have big muscles  [Music]  that pie smells wonderful young master  if i may might i add a sprinkle of  powdered sugar on top to give it an  extra touch of sweetness  [Music]  what the [ __ ] is this  bottle b did you use my truffles from  the bottom drawer in the fridge  i told you the drawers of limits  this bag of truffles cost me 20 billion  dollars  there's no need to make such a fusser  they are merely truffles  and besides the boy clearly didn't even  know they were so important  quiet butler this is family business  you're a butler a battler  sir bart levy are you going to let him  speak to me like that  you are dismissed alfred  wait alfred i didn't mean  that's quite all right young master your  father's right i am merely a butler  nothing more  i'll go back to the basement and eat my  bland oatmeal that you gave me for  dinner  yeah and make sure you remember to lock  it this time so you don't get out [ __ ]  you give me that pie now  i want it  no daddy what are you going to do with  that pipe i need it for school tomorrow  i'll show you what i'm going to do  no father don't do it i beg  okay class everybody put your books away  because it's time to celebrate bartlebee  and cliff's birthday  now i want each and every one of you  babies to give him a great picture  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  what's the hold up partly go get that  snack out of your shoe cubby to pass  around  [Music]  wow blueberry that's my favorite flavor  gimme gimme  [Music]  [Music]  yuck  why does it taste like somebody planted  their butt crack on this pie  i think there's a poop stain on my piece  i kind of like it  [Music]  what is wrong my dear why does your  heart ache so  nah [ __ ] i'm i'm just so happy that you  can finally draw a piece of pie made by  me and my own two hands  oh god that tastes absolutely horrible  what kind of pie is this supposed to  be i concur  it tastes like my runny [ __ ]  after a night out eating nacho bowls at  carlos o'kelly's  what no it doesn't my son how can this  be  we use the most expensive ingredients  that money can't buy  let me have a piece of that the fools  are right it does taste like [ __ ]  but dad that doesn't make sense  the only ones who touched it were and we  have the monthly golden touch  we weren't the only ones you dumb [ __ ]  what do you put in this pie tell me now  what do you think i [ __ ] crapped in  it  that's what you get for always calling  me ugly all the time  you are ugly [ __ ]  whatever the case we must rate the spy  as it is  no you can't do this [ __ ] tell them to  wait i can go make another pie just give  me 10 minutes  if we break the rules for you then we  have to break the rules for everyone  and we can't do that i'm sorry sir but  it's time for you to go  and so it is  does everyone have their scores in their  hats  yep  bart levy montclair of dresden and his  family's pie earns them a total of 13  points  will the next contestant please step up  to the plate  greetings we call our pie  god's thick  and sticky love  no we don't  yo  thank you again yakuza for letting me  use this empty warehouse to house my  captured prisoners  shut up you ping pong  rice munching [ __ ] i'm pooping  right now  [Applause]  well  oh no i heard you the first time i just  don't give a [ __ ] i won't let you do  this i did not capture that man just so  you can't steal him from me  my mission is not yet done i need him  for leverage against the sonic  underground  foreign  it's full of paper bombs run for your  lives kids  you tricked me the yakuza really are as  fearsome as they say  or  hmm  are you sure that canada is here  professor  of course and so will be sonic the  hedgehog and his siblings there is no  way a traditional rural white family  would pass up the opportunity to visit  the county fair when it comes to town  professor i see him  he's over there taking part in the pie  bake off  and i think i see sonic with him too  looks like our luck is turning around  attaboy little billy  now spread out like you are spreading  the cheeks we have to track down it  there before the akusa lose patience  with us  eight-year-olds ready her fists we  strike immediately  and just like that with their tasty  apple pie the echidna family earns a  total of 19 points  immediately putting them in the lead for  this year's contest  we did it there we might actually stand  a chance at winning now  now knuckles don't you see it wasn't us  we only have god to thank because god is  the one who made this all possible when  he made her four thousand years ago  that's a nice story [ __ ] too bad  science would have to disagree with your  ass  hey can't you see we're in the middle of  a competition here  get lost  shut up we are the ones making demands  that's right now we're going to tie you  up and take you to professor majorcore's  sex dungeon  and we don't want to hear any complaints  are we clear  bro we have to run  bro  bro  hey where are you taking my bro  professor major court i found him i  found sonic the hedgehog get your  stinking hands off of me you little runt  let go  [Music]  [Applause]  occupied and i just had a chicken taco  so i would highly recommend you go look  for another porta potty  barley you have to make haste quickly  somebody is out here kidnapping your  [ __ ] [ __ ]  what how do you know this  i see it happening right now they're  taking him away  if you don't hurry you won't ever be  able to [ __ ] him again  [ __ ] looks like i don't have time to  wipe my ass  professor it's bartleby  oh god no this wasn't a part of the plan  kids you know the drill  get in wall formation and protect your  leader  i want to see a wall at least twice as  effective as the one at the mexican  border  that's all boss that won't be so hard  at long last major chord you finally  decide to show your cowardly face  and even now you choose to hide in the  shadows like a scared baby who's pooped  his typey and too ashamed to tell his  daddy about it  what can i say  when you gotta go you gotta go  now if you excuse me i'll be leaving  with my prize  well sorry to say you're not going  anywhere for your biggest mistake was  being born in the same time period as i  now i'm going to ask only once release  the boy  are you really not going to like what  happens next oh  really now i'm interested do you plan on  harming the lives of v sweet innocent  children  what's he doing he's just standing there  look  say  [Music]  is  did you see the signal  yes  the one with bartleby's hands raised  straight up to the sky  then it's time this is why i graduated  from harvard university i've always  dreamed of this day  it's funny how history days feel so  normal why you are living them  go on jeremy release it  release the gauntlet of dresden  the gauntlet of dresden are you certain  just one punch from this thing has the  power to flat in a small city or destroy  the very fabric of space and time and  the omniverse as we know it  that's right and that is why only one  man can use it barnaby montclair of  dresden and he calls for it now  tell me rookie are you ballsy enough to  deny that man his wishes  [Music]  tell me what i'm feeling  [Music]  my body flows  [Music]  [Music]  upside down  set me upside down  tell me that you're feeling  [Music]  no it cannot be i was told because of  dresden was merely a myth a fairy tale  told to children to give them hope  if that's what you were told then you  were lied to for i know it's real  because i use it to destroy my [ __ ]  [ __ ] on a nightly basis [ __ ] this i'm  out of here  i'll get you [ __ ]  ahem bart levy we would like you to have  this  what you're giving me the bake off  trophy but i do not understand all i did  was save your life and prevent you from  being raped  of course  and ain't that the point of pie  to make people happy  if you ask me nobody has ever made as  many people as happy as you did here  today  hey i guess you were right maybe i do  deserve this trophy more than everyone  else who spent the entire tiered last  night and this morning baking their  fights and yet won't even get a chance  to enter them in the contest  well why the heck is everyone just  standing around for my first declaration  is the pie bake off champion  free banana cream ties for everybody  [Applause]  [Music]  we fight the unknown  on a journey but  oh what's waiting i don't know  i'm trying not to let go  [Music]  but  it  up  [Applause]  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]  i will  [Music]  oh  [Music]  [Applause]  [Music]